# ADEYEMI ADEOLUWA ABRAHAM

## **ABOUT ME**

Driven Student leveraging studies in Electrical and Electronics Engineering and equally gaining skills in software development who is easily able to adapt to new environments and has excellent organizational and positive interpersonal skills who is also highly motivated, organized and target oriented seeks real-world experience as an Electrical and Computer Engineer.

## CONTACT



engraaadevemi@gmail.com



+2348069269046



Ilorin, Kwara State, Nigeria

#### Website:

https://jesuisabraham.netlify.app/

## **SKILLS**

SCSS JAVASCRIPT

REACTJS GIT

HTML/CSS SOLIDITY

# **EDUCATION**

## ST. MARY PRIMARY SCHOOL, ILORIN

FIRST LEAVING SCHOOL CERTIFICATE

2004 -

2010

## **EFFECTIVE INTERNATIONAL COLLEGE, ILORIN**

SECONDARY SCHOOL CERTIFICATE 2010 – 2016

#### **COVENANT UNIVERSITY, OTA**

Bachelor of Engineering 2016 - 2022

(SECOND-CLASS UPPER DIVISIONS (76%)

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

<u>INTERN</u>

Apr, 2016 - Jul, 2016

#### **Lapariah Technologies Limited**

- Reported Back to instructor to receive day-to-day tasks and responsibilities
- Support components from users and customers.
- Installation of Wireles Services

#### INTERN

May, 2018 – Aug, 2018

#### Newsong Global Technologies, Ilorin, Kwara State

- Reported Back to instructor to receive day-to-day tasks and responsibilities
- Solar Panel Installation Team Member
- Solar Water Pump Installation Team Member
- Installation of all related Solar technological equipment
- Delivered clerical support by handling range of routine and special requirements

## **EXPERTISE**

**TECHNOLOGY** 

**COMMUNICATION** 

**WEB DEVELOPMENT** 

TIME MANAGEMENT

**CLIENT SERVICE** 

## **AWARDS**

GOOGLE IT SUPPORT CERTIFICATE

ISSUED BY COURSERA / MAR - 2022

INTRODUCTION TO CLOUD COMPUTING

ISSUED BY COURSERA/ MAR - 2022

MOTOR AND MOTOR CIRCUITS

ISSUED BY COURSERA/ JUL -2021

FUNDAMENTALS OF NETWORK COMMUNICATION

ISSUED BY COURSERA/ JUN - 2021

**CONVERTER CONTROL** 

ISSUED BY COURSERA/ JAN - 2022

## WORK EXPERIENCE CONTINUED

#### INTERN

Mar, 2020 - May, 2020

#### **SCHLUMBERGER**

- Oversaw daily operations to ensure high levels of productivity
- Used critical thinking to break down problems, evaluated solutions and make decisions
- Reported Back to instructor to receive day-to-day tasks and responsibilities

#### INTERN

Aug, 2020 – Nov, 2020

Redeemers University (Electrical and Electronics Engineering Department), Ede, Osun State

- Actively listened to students, handled concerns quickly and escalated major issues to the Head of Department
- Oversaw daily operations to ensure high levels of productivity
- Used critical thinking to break down problems, evaluated solutions and make decisions
- Assisting the Dean and Head of the Department in lectures and other class related activities
- Assisting in Laboratory and Practical Electrical Engineering Experiments
- Took part in a One (1) year Community Development Service for the country